Guide to the Richard Marshall Collection of Gay Erotica and Pornography MSS.498
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. Magazines and Serials, 1948-2011, undated; 8 Linear Feet in 8 record cartons.
  - Subseries II.A. Magazines, 1948-2011, undated; 6.25 Linear Feet in 6 record cartons and 2 flat file folders.
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1988, v.7 n.6 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1988, v.8 n.1 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1988, v.8 n.2 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1988, v.8 n.3 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1989, v.8 n.4 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1989, v.8 n.5 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1989, v.9 n.1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1989, v.9 n.2 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1990, v.9 v.4 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1990, v.9 n.5 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1990, v.10 n.2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1990, v.10 n,3 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1991, v.10 n.4 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1991, v.10 n.5 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1991, v.11 n.2 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1991, v.11 n.3 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1992, v.11 n.4 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1992, v.11 n.5 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1992, v.11 n.6 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1992, v.12 n.1 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1994, v.13 n.4 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Stroke, Stroke, Undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Stud, n.3, Undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Surge, Feb-April, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - The Target Album, New York, Target Studio, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - They Shoot Homos Don't They, Australia, Oct 2005, n.2 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Titplay, California, Le Salon, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Trixx, Paris, Ilico Magazine, n.3, Undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Trixx, Paris, Ilico Magazine, n.6, Undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Toy, n.173, Undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Toy, n.177, Undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Toy, n.178, Undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Toy, n.179, Undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Toy, n.180, Undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Toy: Best of, Undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Versace, Fall/Winter, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Versace Sport. Autumn/Winter, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Very Uncut, n.1, Undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Water Boys, California, Water Boys, Winter 1997, Issue 8 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Water Boys, California, Water Boys, Spring 1998, Issue 9 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Water Boys, California, Water Boys, Spring 2000, Issue 13 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - The Zeus Collection, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - The Zeus Collection, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Zing Magazine: A Curatorial Crossing, New York, Zing LLC, Winter/Spring 2003, issue 18 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Zing Magazine: A Curatorial Crossing, New York, Zing LLC, 2006/7, issue 21, 2006-2007 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Zing Magazine: A Curatorial Crossing, New York, Zing LLC, issue 21, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Subseries II.B. Serials, 1981-2000; 2 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons.
    This subseries contains serials featuring erotic stories and readers' letters. Many titles are comprised of stories compiled from other zines and magazines.
    Material is in alphabetical order by publication title, then chronologically by issue number and/or publication date.
    - Bear Tales, FirstHand Publications. Jan., 1994 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Beau Presents: Cherry Boys. New York, Sport-Omatic Publishing. May 1996, v.3 n.4 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Biker Tales. New Jersey, FirstHand Publications. March, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Family Sex Tales. New Jersey, FirstHand Publications. April, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Jockstrap Tales. New Jersey, FirstHand Publications. July, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Homosexual Encounters from "First Hand": Hot Acts. California, Gay Sunshine Press. 1984. v.1 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Homosexual Encounters from "First Hand": Hot Studs. California, G. S. Press. 1986. v.3 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Homosexual Encounters from "First Hand": Singlehanded. California, Leyland Publications. 1987. v4 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Homosexual Encounters from "First Hand": When I Was 18. California, Leyland Publications. 1988. v5 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. August 1990. v.6 n.6 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. July 1991. v.7 n.5 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. Nov 1991. v.7 n.9 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. Dec 1991. v.7 n.10 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. Jan 1992. v.7 n.11 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. Feb 1992. v.7 n.12 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. April 1992. v.8 n.2 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. May 1992. v.8 n.3 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. July 1992. v.8 n.5 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. August 1992. v.8 n.6 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. October 1992. v.8 n.8 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. Nov 1992. v.8 n.9 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. March 1993. v.9 n.1 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. June 1993. v.9 n.4 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. July 1993. v.9 n.5 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. Nov 1993. v.9 n.9 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. Jan 1994. v.9 n.11 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. March 1994. v.10 n.1 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. April 1994. v.10 n.2 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. May 1994. v.10 n.3 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. Aug 1994. v.10 n.6 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. Sept 1994. v.10 n.9 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. Oct 1994. v.10 n.8 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. Dec 1994. v.10 n.10 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Manscape. First Hand Publications. Jan 1996. v.11 n.10 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Mantalk. FirstHand Publications. Sept 1997. v.6 n.9 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Men's Room & Truck Stops. New York, Thrust Industries. Oct., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Raunch Tales. New Jersey, FirstHand Publications. April, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Tearoom Tales. New Jersey, FIrstHand Publications. Jan., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Tearoom Tales. New Jersey, FIrstHand Publications. Nov., 1994 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Tearoom Tales. New Jersey, FIrstHand Publications. Nov., 1995 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Trucker Tales. New Jersey, FirstHand Publications. 1989. Issue 1 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - True Gay Encounters: Lust. California, Leyland Publications. 1994. v.1 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - True Gay Encounters: Hard. California, G. S. Press. 1986. v.2 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - True Gay Encounters: Manplay. California, Leyland Publications. 1987. v.3 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - True Gay Encounters: Young Numbers. California, Leyland Publications. 1988. v.4 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - True Gay Encounters: Humongous. California, Leyland Publications. 1988. v.5, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - True Gay Encounters: 10 1/2 Inches. California, Leyland Publications. 1989. v.6 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - True Gay Encounters: Boys, Boys, Boys! California, Leyland Publications. 1989. v.7 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - True Gay Encounters: Studflesh. California, Leyland Publications. 1990. v.8 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - True Gay Encounters: Boys Will Be Boys. California, Leyland Publications. 1990. v.9 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - True Gay Encounters: Eighteen and Over. California, Leyland Publications. 1991. v.10 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - True Gay Experiences of Foreskin and Circumcision: Cut/Uncut. California, G. S. Press. 1986. v.1 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - True Homosexual Experiences, A S.T. H. Chapbook: Smut. New York, Gay Presses of New York. 1984. v5 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - True Homosexual Experiences, An S. T. H. Chapbook: Raunch. Boston, Fidelity. 1990. v11 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - True Homosexual Experiences, An S. T. H. Chapbook: Lewd. Boston, Fidelity. 1992. v12 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - True Homosexual Experiences from S. T. H. (Straight to Hell) Writers: Meat. California, Gay Sunshine Press. 1981. v1 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - True Homosexual Experiences from S. T. H. Writers: Meat. 4th ed. California, Gay Sunshine Press. 1994. v1 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - True Homosexual Experiences from S. T. H. Writers: Flesh. California, Gay Sunshine Press. 1982. v2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - True Homosexual Experiences from S. T. H. Writers: Flesh. 3rd ed. California, Gay Sunshine Press.1997. v2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - True Homosexual Experiences from S. T. H. Writers: Sex. California, Gay Sunshine Press.1982. v3 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - True Homosexual Experiences from S. T. H. Writers: Sex. 3rd ed. California, Gay Sunshine Press.1997. v3 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - True Homosexual Experiences from S. T. H. Writers: Juice. California, Gay Sunshine Press.1984. v5 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - True Homosexual Experiences from S. T. H. Writers: Wads. California, Gay Sunshine Press. 1985. v6 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - True Homosexual Experiences from S. T. H. Writers: Wads. 2nd ed. California, Gay Sunshine Press. 2000. v6 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - True Homosexual Experiences from S. T. H. Writers: Cream. California, G. S.Press. 1986. v7 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - True Homosexual Experiences from S. T. H. Writers: Cream. 2nd ed. California, G. S. Press/Leyland Publications. 1995. v7 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - True Homosexual Military Stories: Enlisted Meat. California, Leyland Publications. 1991. v.1 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - True Homosexual Military Stories: Warriors & Lovers. California, Leyland Publications. 1992. v.2 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - True Homosexual Military Stories: Military Sex. California, Leyland Publications. 1993. v.3 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - True Homosexual Military Stories: Macho Marines California, Leyland Publications. 1997. v.6 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - True Revelations and Strange Happenings from 18 Wheeler: Trash. California, Gay Sunshine Press. 1985. v.1 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - True Revelations and Strange Happenings from 18 Wheeler: Trucker. California, Gay Sunshine Press. 1986. v.2 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - True Revelations and Strange Happenings from 18 Wheeler: Sex Stop. California, Leyland Publications. 1987. v.3 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - True Revelations and Strange Happenings from 18 Wheeler: Head Stops. California, Leyland Publications. 1988. v.4 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - True Revelations and Strange Happenings from 18 Wheeler: Meat Rack. California, Leyland Publications. 1992. v.6 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - True Revelations and Strange Happenings from 18 Wheeler: Rough Trade. California, Leyland Publications. 1996. v.7 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Uniform Tales. New Jersey, FirstHand Publication. September, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Series III. Zines, 1964-2009, undated; 2 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons.
  Material is in alphabetical order by zine title, followed by issue number and/or publication date.
  This series contains zines, which include erotic stories, pictures, writings, and reader-submitted content. Some zines were produced by lesser-known gay porn producers and production companies, while others evolved into formal magazine publications during their print run.
  - American Cream. Ed. Pats, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Bad Seeds. Ed. Bo Wakeman. New York. Issue 3, Undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Bike Boy. London, HIM Hot Strips. Issue 37, Undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Born to Kill Fanzine (Cheesebike #6). Ed. Pat McCarthy. Marseille. Spring 2013. Issue 50 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Born to Kill Fanzine (Pigeoning Zine #5). Ed. Pat McCarthy. New York. June 2013. Issue 52 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Boys Speak Out: On Man/Boy Love. Ed. David Miller. New York, North American Man/Boy Love Association (NAMBLA). July, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Brief Tales. New Hope Products. v.1 issue 8, Undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Brief Tales. New Hope Products. v.1 issue 7, Undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Brief Tales. New Hope Products. Aug/Sept 1997. v.11 n.11 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Brief Tales. New Hope Products. Oct-Dec 1997. v.11 n.12 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Celebrate the Self; The Magazine of Solo Sex. Alabama, Factor Press. May-June 1997. v.5 n.3 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Commando 3, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Cowpokes. Ed. John Tomes and Mark Anderson. Wyoming, MJ Enterprises. Dec./Jan 1994-5. Issue 4, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Cowpokes. Ed. John Tomes and Mark Anderson. Wyoming, MJ Enterprises. Feb/March 1995. Issue 5 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Cowpokes. Ed. John Tomes and Mark Anderson. Wyoming, MJ Enterprises. Aug/Sept 1996. Issue 14 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Cowpokes. Ed. John Tomes and Mark Anderson. Wyoming, MJ Enterprises. Sept/Oct 1996. Issue 20 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Cowpokes. Ed. John Tomes and Mark Anderson. Wyoming, MJ Enterprises. Aug/Sept 1997. Issue 20 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Dirty. Ed. Chris Leslie. New York, J & H Publications. Feb. 1994. v.1 issue 2 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Dirty. Ed. Chris Leslie. New York, J & H Publications. March 1994. v.1 issue 3 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Dirty. Ed. Chris Leslie. New York, J & H Publications. April 1994. v.1 issue 4 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Dirty. Ed. Chris Leslie. New York, J & H Publications. July 1994. v.1 issue 5 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Dirty. Ed. Chris Leslie. New York, J & H Publications. Jan 1995. v.2 Issue 1 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Dirty. Ed. Chris Leslie. New York, J & H Publications. June 1995. v.2 issue 2 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Dirty. Ed. Chris Leslie. New York, J & H Publications. May 1996. v.2. n.4 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Dirty. Ed. Chris Leslie. New York, J & H Publications. July 1998. v.3 n.2 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Dog Daze. Ed. Damon Blows. v.2, Undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Dog Daze. Ed. Damon Blows. Seattle, Treasure Island Media. v.4-5, Undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Drunk on Cum. Ed. Paul and Kevin. Berkeley, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - The Erotic Misadventures of Black Latex Pansy. n.1, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Farm. New York, Feature and Instituting Contemporary Idea, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Florida Tales. Ed. Robert J. Handcock. Handjobs Publication, Undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Etienne. The Grecian Guild Studio Quarterlyy: Presents Etienne. Washington, D.C. n.8, Undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Feb, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Mar., 1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Oct., 1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Nov., 1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Dec., 1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Jan., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Feb., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Mar., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, April, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Handjobs.California, Avenue Services, May, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, July, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Aug., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Sept., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Oct., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Nov., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Dec., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Jan., 1994 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Feb., 1994 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Mar., 1994 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, April, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, May, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, June, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, July, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Aug., 1994 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Sept., 1994 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Nov., 1994 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Dec., 1994 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Jan.- May, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, June, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Aug., 1995 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Sept., 1995 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Nov., 1995 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Dec., 1995 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Feb., 1996 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, March, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, July, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Sept., 1996 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Oct., 1996 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Nov., 1996 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Dec., 1996 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Feb., 1997 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, March, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, May, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Handjobs. California, Avenue Services, Aug., 1997 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Handjobs Anthology. California, Avenue Services. 2001. v.4 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Handjobs Anthology. California, Avenue Services. 2001. v.8 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Handjobs Anthology. California, Avenue Services. 2002. v.9 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Handjobs Anthology. California, Avenue Services. 2007. v.15 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Handjobs by Julius: Back Alley Graffiti. California, Avenue Services, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Handjobs by Julius: Bavarian Chronicles I, the Legacy of Slava. California, Avenue Services, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Handjobs Presents Bedtime Dad's Tales. California, Avenue Services. 2006. v.5 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Holy Titclamps. Ed. Laurence "Larry-bob" Roberts. n.15, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - The Hun Book of Bondage. Portland, The Hun. Issue 2, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Hun Comics: 'B' series, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Hun Comics. Jan 1988. n.1 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Hun Comics. June 1990. n.5 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Hun Comics. May 1992. n.6 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Hun Comics. Feb 1994. n.7 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Hun Comics. Jan. 1996. n.8 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Hun Comics. Portland, The Hun. Aug 1996. n.9 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Hun Comics. Portland, The Hun, Dec 1997. n.10 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Hun Comics. Portland, The Hun. Nov 1998. n.11 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Hun Comics. Portland, The Hun. April 2002. n.12 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Jack & The Jungle (Tom of Finland). v.1/2/3, Undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - J.D.s., Undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Joezine. New York, Killer & Butch. n.2, Undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Kake, by Tom of Finland. Barcelona, Candango. n.3, Undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Kake. Barcelona, Candango. n.4, Undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Kake. Barcelona, Candango. n.5, Undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Kake, Special Edition: Greasy Rider. Denmark. n.21, Undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - The Male Figure. California, Bruce of Los Angeles. v.12, Undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Manorama. Washington D. C., Manorama Enterprises. November 1965. n.26 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Man Power! New York, Colt Studio. n.1, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Men into Underwear. Ed. John T. and Mark A. Wyoming, MJ Enterprises, Mar/April 1995. n.11 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Men into Underwear. Ed. John T. and Mark A. Wyoming, MJ Enterprises, Nov/Dec. 1996. n.21 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Men into Underwear. Ed. John T. and Mark A. Wyoming, MJ Enterprises, Mar/April 1997. n.23 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Men into Underwear. Ed. John T. and Mark A. Wyoming, MJ Enterprises, Sept/Oct. 1997. n.26 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Mentor. California, S.C.M.A. Fall, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Mentor. California, S.C.M.A. n.7, Undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Mentor. California, S.C.M.A. n.9, Undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Monstar: The Bruce LaBruce Story. Ed. Blab, Liza Lamonica, and k.d. kwellada. n.9, Undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - My Comrade. Ed. Les Simpson. Spring, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - My Comrade. Ed. Les Simpson. New York, My Comrade. Summer, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - My Comrade. Ed. Les Simpson. New York, My Comrade. Winter, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - My Comrade. Ed. Les Simpson. New York, My Comrade. Fall, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - My Comrade. Ed. Les Simpson. New York, My Comrade, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Naked Magazine. Ed. Christopher Arroquun. California, Naked Magazine. v.1 n.2, Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Naked Magazine. Ed. Christopher Arroquun. California, Naked Magazine. v.1 n.4, Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Nasty Boyz. Ed. Anthony Panther. New Jersey, ATKOL. 1995. v.1 n.1 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Nasty Boyz. Ed. Anthony Panther. New Jersey, ATKOL. 1995. v.1 n.2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Nasty Boyz. Ed. Anthony Panther. New Jersey, ATKOL. 1995. v.1 n.3 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Not Fade Away: Selections from the NAMBLA Bulletin. New York, The North American Man/Boy Love Association, Undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Pansy Beat. Ed. Michael Economy, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Photographorama: A Photographic Comparison of Nationalities, Undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Pisszine. Ed. Massimo Magrini. n.6, Undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - The Polished Knob. Ed. A.F. Gillit. Massachusetts, Planet 23 Productions. Winter 1994. n.2 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - The Polished Knob. Ed. A.F. Gillit. Massachusetts, Planet 23 Productions. Summer 1994. n.4 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - The Polished Knob. Ed. A.F. Gillit. Massachusetts, Planet 23 Productions. 1994. Issue 5 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - The Polished Knob. Ed. A.F. Gillit. Massachusetts, Planet 23 Productions. 1995. Issue 6 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - The Polished Knob. Ed. A.F. Gillit. Massachusetts, Planet 23 Productions. 1995. Issue 7 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Pup. n.3, Undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Raunch. Ed. Tom Stevens. Arizona. v.1 n.1, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Raunch. Ed. Tom Stevens. Arizona. v.1 n.2, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Raunch. Ed. Tom Stevens. Arizona. v.1 n.3, Undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Raunch. Ed. Tom Stevens. Arizona. v.1 n.4, Undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Raunch. Ed. Tom Stevens. Arizona. v.1 n.5, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Raunch. Ed. Tom Stevens. Arizona. v.1 n.6, Undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Rim Reader. n.61, Undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Sexvibe. Ed. Charlie Medrano. California, The Sex Essentials Network. Aug. 1994. n.3 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Skirts. Ed. Pat McCunthy, Undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Sludgemaster. Texas. n.14, Undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Sludgemaster. Texas. n.15, Undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Southern Cumfort. Georgia, HOT! Publishing Company, 1994. v.1 n.3 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Spunk: JizBiz Guide. v.3 n.6, Undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - The Stall, by Tom of Finland, Stephen, Etienne. COQ International. n.2, Undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Straight to Hell: "The Manhattan Review of Unnatural Acts". Ed. Billy Miller. New York. 1978. n.42 (Box 15, Folder 17)